原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译    @少年影视派    油腻希
翻译     洗七里    前妻客串赛钱钱
校对    新浪微博@赛太公
时间轴   三水
后期    加森
总监    生无可恋瓜
家  庭
摩  登
第十一季 第十集
这个是我送的  这丝带算不上我的最佳作品
This one's from me. The ribboning isn't my best --
我患了腕管综合症
I have carpal tunnel.
我的新公司安排我入住了普雷斯科综合生活馆
My new company is putting me up at The Prescott,
一个奢华的住所  配备各种服务
a luxury residence with full amenities.
我承认  这种奢侈的生活
I admit, this extravagant lifestyle
让我有那么一点不舒服
can make me a little uncomfortable.
轻点  玛塔
Gentle, Marta!
又是蜡烛  谢谢了啊  各位
Another candle. Thanks, everyone.
艾丽克斯  你应该知道
Alex, you should know
楼下美发沙龙里的那个骗子
that a crook works at the hair salon downstairs --
威尼斯的阿道夫
Adolfo of Venice.
他不是给那些明星染发的吗
Isn't he the colorist to the stars?
谢谢询问  尽管我知道你知道这个事实
Thank you for asking even though I know you know.
我恨他
I hate him.
威尼斯的阿道夫实际上是
Adolfo of Venice is actually
贝克斯菲尔德的阿伦・卡普曼
Alan Carpman of Bakersfield.
我们当年一起成为理发师
We started as hairdressers together,
但他窃取了我的染发剂配方
but he stole my hair dye formula.
对于一个满是可爱成员的家庭来说
For a family of generally lovely people,
我们有好多宿敌啊
we sure have a lot of rivals.
虽然大家在这里很开心  但你们该走了
You know what, it's been fun, but it's time to go.
你还没拆开我和小卡送给你的蜡烛呢
You haven't even opened the candle that Cam and I got you.
我们不能参观一下整栋大楼吗
And don't we get a tour of the building?
这地方什么都有
This place has everything.
射箭场  鲨鱼池  以及...
Um, an archery range, a shark tank, a --
竟然还有西部世界
a Westworld?
抱歉  我有个大项目得交工了
Sorry, I've got a huge project due.
我们可以自己去探索
We can always just explore on our own.
实际上  你们不行
Actually, you can't.
公司有严格规定  客人都要在员工陪伴下才行
There's a strict "No unaccompanied guests" policy.
一旦我违反了  他们就会把我赶走
I violate that, they kick me out.
我会让泊车员把你们的车开出来的
I'll have the valet fetch your cars.
从这里就可以安排吗
Oh, you can do that from here?
是啊  一切都是自动的
Yeah, everything's automated.
只需要有住户身份码就可以了
You just need a resident ID code.
-再见  菲尔  -再见
- Bye, Phil. ?- Bye.
好了  我把车停在路旁了
All right, well, I parked on the street,
我们回家见吧
so I'll just meet you at home.
-再见  克莱尔  -我需要去一趟商场
- Bye, Claire. - I need to run to the mall.
你能从农贸市场买些牛排晚上吃吗
Would you pick up some steaks from the farmers market for tonight?
所以你还记得今晚是约会之夜
Oh, so you did remember it's date night.
你没回我的无纸化邀请函  让我还有点担心呢
I was a little worried after your response to my Paperless Post.
拜托
Oh, come on.
你知道我说的"或许"最终都是"确定参加"
You know my maybes always turn into will attends.
好的
Okay.
你和我上一次
When was the last time that you and I
一起准备浪漫晚餐是什么时候了
cooked a romantic dinner together?
我们上周才弄过啊
We did it last week.
我说的可不是简单地把热狗片撒在披萨上
I'm not talking about sprinkling hot dog slices on a DiGiorno's.
你就不能在我挨说之前把车开来吗
You couldn't bring my car before I got in trouble?
谢谢
Thank you.
我一直悄悄在网上当美食博主
I've been secretly moonlighting as an online food blogger,
账号叫"帽衫美食家"
"Foodie in a Hoodie"
是一个押韵的名字
it rhymes on the page.
我很快就收获了一大批粉丝
I've quickly developed a huge following,
普雷斯科综合生活馆有着全市最火的餐厅
and The Prescott is home to the city's hottest restaurant,
叫"什么餐厅"
called Pardon.
你好
Hello.
您好  先生
Ah, good day, sir.
请原谅  我是新来的
Forgive me. I'm new here.
我还在努力认识这里所有的住户
Still getting to know each of the tenants.
我是这里的管理员希金斯
I'm your concierge, Higgins.
你看着好眼熟啊  我们以前见过吗
You look so familiar. Have we met?
恐怕没有
'Fraid not, no.
不过经常有人这么说
I do get that a lot, though.
我长着一张大众脸  大众身材
I have an everyman face and body.
机器人崛起了
They're rising.
没错  芬利
Ah, yes, Finley.
它负责巡查大楼  搜出非住户
Patrols the building for non-residents
全靠运动感应器和面部扫描仪
using a motion sensor and face scanner.
确实非常有用  但它拥有独特的人类本事
Useful, yes, but does he have that uniquely human ability
能提前预料到人的每一项需求吗
to anticipate a person's every need?
喝椰子水吗
Coconut water?
我都没意识到我想喝水呢
I didn't even know I wanted this!
芬利  走开
Finley, away!
还有什么能帮到您的吗  先生
Anything else I can help you with, sir?
没了  我直接去餐厅
No. I'm just headed down to the restaurant.
什么
Pardon?
你们的  内部食堂
Your...in-house eatery.
什么
Pardon?
就是  服务生  餐具  每日特色菜
You know -- uh, waiters, cutlery, daily specials.
好像是叫"什么餐厅"
I think it's called Pardon.
-当然了  我的错  -没事
- Of course. My mistake. - It's all right.
请这边走
Right this way.
要躲避安保机器人会很棘手
Avoiding the security robot would be tricky,
但芬利有个弱点
but Finley had a weakness --
它只能侦测到在移动的人
he can only detect people if they're moving.
那值得冒险啊
And it was worth the risk --
"什么餐厅"的小汉堡号称是全世界最美味的
Pardon claimed to have the world's best beef slider,
我的粉丝全都超想看到我的点评
and my -- my followers are dying for a review.
除了一个人
Well, all but one.
我有个黑子
I have a troll.
网名叫"厨巨王走"  鬼知道那是什么
Screen name "Close to Utlaw," Wherever that is.
我们最近在评论里发生了撕逼大战
We recently got into a -- a heated comment war.
脏话乱飚  操爹骂娘
Insults were hurled, mothers disparaged.
谁能想到网络这么负能量呢
Who knew the Internet could be so negative?
一人位  我住这里
Table for one. I live here.
刚出来个空桌
Something just opened up.
好极了  带路吧  我住这里
Great, lead the way. I live here.
嗨  我初来乍到
Hi. Uh, I'm new here.
你能领我去放映室吗
Could you lead me to the screening room?
我觉得可以吧
I should think so.
在管家学院  我在领路方面可是全班第一名
At the butler academy, I led my class in leading.
这边请
This way.
最近  我搞到了有史以来
Recently, I got a special edition Blu-ray
最伟大的电影《阿拉伯的劳伦斯》的蓝光盘
of the best movie ever made, "Lawrence of Arabia."
据传  普雷斯科综合生活馆
Word is, The Prescott has
拥有最顶尖的放映室  带环绕声
a state-of-the-art screening room with surround sound.
知道它没有什么吗
Know what it doesn't have?
曼尼
Manny.
拜托  我觉得这里用推拉镜头才更合适吧
Hello! I would've gone with a tracking shot there.
希望他在沙漠里能找到精彩情节
I sure hope he finds a plot out there in that desert.
看吧  我们出名的糖果墙
Behold, our famous candy wall.
嘿  甜心宝宝
Hey, Sugar Babies.
什么事  糖心贝贝
Yes, honey buns?
不  甜心宝宝是有史以来最适合看电影时吃的糖
?No, Sugar Babies. The greatest movie candy of all time.
万分抱歉
A thousand apologies.
我马上去给您弄一些来
I will track some down for you straight away.
-你不介意吗  -介意什么  拜托
- You wouldn't mind? - Mind? Please.
我最大的乐趣
There is no greater joy
就是去搞到一些我从未听过的东西
than fetching something I've never heard of
给一个我刚认识的人
for someone I've only just met.
请问有什么需要帮忙的吗
May I help you with something?
不用  我只是在等人而已
No, I'm just -- I'm waiting for someone.
那个人叫大卫・贝克汉姆
And his name is David Beckham.
他就住在普雷斯科综合生活馆
Resident at The Prescott.
米奇很讨厌我做这种事
Okay, Mitchell hates it when I do this,
但我每次遇见名人
but every time I meet a celebrity,
我都拜托他们帮我录来电语音应答
I ask them to record my outgoing message.
我现在用的是我在银行遇到史诺普・道格时录的
My current one is from when I saw Snoop Dogg at a bank.
嘻哈巨星
抱歉我没看见你  如你所见
Sorry I missed you. As you can see --
老子在忙
I'm busy!
有时事情会...
And sometimes things can --
离老子远点
Get away from me!
请留言  并留下你的电话号码
Please leave a message, including your phone number,
那是为了...保安[安全着想]
just for -- ?Security!
宝贝  什么事  我这会儿有点忙
Hey, sweetie, what's up? I'm -- I'm kind of busy.
小卡  我受伤了  是我的腿
Cam, I'm hurt. It's my leg.
什么
What?
我在美食街滑倒了
I slipped in the food court,
现在全身都粘粘的  而且还被十岁小屁孩嘲笑
and I'm all sticky and tweens are laughing at me.
你一定要来接我
You have to come pick me up.
听起来好惨  但是
Well, that sounds awful, but --
克莱尔不是离你更近吗
Isn't -- Isn't Claire closer?
可你就在街尾的农贸市场啊
Well, you're at the farmers market right down the street.
行吧  我这就来
Okay, fine. I'm on my way.
老公你最好啦
Aww, you're the best.
我绝不能让小卡毁了我当面感谢
I was not gonna let Cam ruin my chance
我的壁纸  维多利亚・贝克汉姆的机会
to thank my wallpaper, Victoria Beckham, one-on-one.
当时是1997年
Okay, so, it was 1997.
我和女朋友在底特律看辣妹合唱团演唱会
I was in Detroit for a Spice Girls concert with my girlfriend.
我本来打算向她求婚的
I was going to propose to her,
戒指什么的都准备好了
had the ring in my pocket and everything,
结果时髦辣妹从台上径直看向我  并说道
when from the stage, Posh looked right at me and said,
维多利亚・贝克汉姆曾是辣妹合唱团的成员
当时的别名是时髦辣妹
"要直面真正的你  米奇尔"
"Be true to yourself, Mitchell!"
好吧  她说的可能是"密歇根"
Okay, you know, she might've said "Michigan,"
但她当时目光正对着我
but she was looking right at me!
那一晚我受到她的鼓舞而出柜
She inspired me to come out that night.
我把那颗钻石挂到脚链上当幸运符
I had that diamond reset as an anklet charm,
接下来我就夜夜笙歌了
and I was off to the races.
那到底是哪门子的奇葩健身袋啊
What kind of gym bag is that, anyway?
这是挎包  你个无知白痴
It's a satchel, you ignorant sneeze.
你最近好暴躁好讨厌
You have been so unpleasant lately.
与他这态度绝对有关的就是
On a definitely related note,
曼尼有好几个月没做过床上"运动"了
Manny hasn't gotten any action in months.
好吧  除了害他得腕管综合征的运动外
Well, other than whatever gave him carpal tunnel.
幸好普雷斯科综合生活馆有80年代有氧健身操课程
Luckily, The Prescott has an '80s aerobi-cise class,
现场会有很多单身熟女
which will be full of single older ladies.
女人一过40岁就到达一个黄金交叉点
Women hit a sweet spot right after 40
那时她们外表仍然美丽
where they still look great
但对男人的要求大大降低
but their standards have lowered.
你身材保持得不错啊  毕竟你已经...
You're in pretty good shape for someone who's...
42岁  43岁了
42? 43?
我才38
I'm 38.
再见
Bye.
希金斯
Higgins.
贝克汉姆先生  抱歉
Oh, Mr. Beckham. Apologies.
退役足球明星  与维多利亚・贝克汉姆是夫妇
我没戴眼镜时就跟蝙蝠一样眼瞎
Blind as a bat without these bad boys.
我和柯特妮跟保龄球教练约好了
So, myself and Courteney are expecting a bowling instructor.
《老友记》主演之一
麻烦你叫他
Would you have him meet us
到楼下的保龄球馆找我们  好吗
downstairs at the bowling alley, please?
你和考克斯女士要为
You and Ms. Cox getting an edge
周末的名人马拉松保龄球赛大练身手吗
for this weekend's celebrity bowl-a-thon?
我们绝对需要练习
Oh, we'll need it.
你没看到去年比赛他打得有多烂
You should've seen the way he bowled last year.
可那比赛只是要为慈善筹款啊
I mean, it is to raise money for charity.
没错  你总共击倒的18个瓶募到18块钱呢
Yeah, a dollar for each of the 18 pins that you knocked down.
多亏了你  无国界医生们
Thanks to you, Doctors Without Borders
现在成了无痢疾药医生
are now Doctors Without Malaria Pills.
有点毒
A bit harsh.
你看到后面那两位女士了吗
Did you see the two friends in the back?
金发那个喜欢我  褐发那个一直盯着你看
The blond one liked me, and the brunette kept staring at you.
你能怪她吗
Can you blame her?
我跳《加勒比海女王》的舞步  无人能及
No one moves to "Caribbean Queen" Like me.
我正要找你们
Ah, just who I was told to be on the lookout for.
有两个人叫你们
A certain couple have asked
去保龄球馆找他们
that you meet them in the bowling alley.
是不是一位金发  一位棕发的
Was it a blonde and a brunette?
没错  而且他们等不及要"开滚"了
Indeed, and they seemed eager to get rolling.
保龄球馆
Bowling alley?
这些妹子口味真重
These girls are freaky.
美发沙龙在哪
Hair salon?
-穿过院子  在您右手边  -谢谢
- Just off the courtyard to your right. - Thank you.
我一直想把头发染成深色
I've always wanted to dye my hair dark.
但我放心委以重任的染发师只有一位
But there's only one colorist I would trust to do it --
威尼斯的阿道夫
Adolfo of Venice.
歌洛莉亚的死对头
Gloria's sworn enemy.
我得偷偷绕回来染发  不让她知道
I just have to sneak back in and do it without her knowing.
妈妈好啊
Hi, Mom.
艾丽克斯  宝贝
Hi, Alex. Hey, honey.
你的项目进展如何
So, how's the project going?
我肯定赶不上最后期限了
I'm never gonna make this deadline.
不会吧  好惨哦
Oh, yeah, no, that -- that -- that's tough...
听到你这么说我很难过
I'm sorry -- sorry to hear that.
工作真是让我压力山大
Work is so stressful.
我得挂了  爱你哦  再见
Yeah, got to go, love you! Bye!
泳池在哪
The pool?
您进电梯
Just hop on the elevator
按下写着"泳池"的大按键就能到达
and press the big button marked "Pool."
众人皆知我是这个家里最大胆无畏的
I am known as the fearless one of the family.
所以克莱尔给我们下周
So, when Claire gave us all free passes
快乐镇水上乐园的免费票后
for the Fun Town Water Park next week,
我不敢承认我怕滑滑梯
I couldn't admit that I am afraid of slides.
水上滑梯速度好快  我觉得自己都要飞出去了
They go so fast, I feel like I'm going to fly off.
我需要先滑一次  到时我就不怕了
I just need to try it once and I am going to be fine.
我做不到
I cannot do it!
不准反悔哦
Hey, no backsies!
好吧  我滑了
Okay, here I go!
你应该让我反悔的
You should have let me do backsies!
住户已进入  美发沙龙
Resident ID access -- hair salon.
什么  谁偷用了我的密码
What? Who's using my code?!
你看起来就像那个女演员
You a-look like that a-actress...
奥黛丽・赫本
Audrey Hepburn.
我是菲尔・邓菲  请留言
This is Phil Dunphy. Leave a message.
菲尔  我晚点有个惊喜送给你
Phil, I have a little surprise for you later.
这么说吧  我知道你有多喜欢褐发美女
Let's just say I know how much you love brunettes.
-菜单给您  -谢谢
- Here's a menu for you. ?- Thank you.
先拍张照片
And for my followers...
吊吊我粉丝们的胃口
an Instagram tease.
您的甜心宝宝  先生
Your Sugar Babies, sir.
希望没让你太费心
I hope it wasn't too much trouble.
恰恰相反
On the contrary.
街对面的公园里正在举办
There was a Mexican birthday celebration
墨西哥生日庆祝会
taking place in the park across the street.
我等他们敲破塞满糖果的皮纳塔后
I waited for the crack of the pinata,
就无耻地混进小孩子中间
mixed in seamlessly with the children,
伺机猛抢糖果
and pounced.
他也在这吗
He's here?!
一个白痴美食博主攻击
Some moron food blogger took a shot
我最喜欢的其中一家餐厅
at one of my favorite spots.
于是我用艺名"橱柜狂徒"去网上骂他
So I go after him using my screen name, "Closet Outlaw."
骂战升级  他唆使他一大票粉丝来围攻我
It escalates, and he turns his army of followers against me.
我就在最后一条评论里写道
As I wrote in my last comment --
"看看是我的拳头硬  还是你的脸硬"
"Let's see how well my fist pairs with your face."
保龄球馆
The bowling alley?!
艾丽克斯在这
Alex is here?!
假如她看到我们  会赶我们出去的
If she sees us, she'll throw us out.
不好意思
Excuse me.
要是金发和棕发那两位来了
If that blonde and brunette come by,
你能不能告诉他们碰面地点换了
could you tell them there's a new meet-up spot?
换成顶楼的按摩浴缸
The hot tubs on the rooftop.
当然  锻炼前先热身
Of course, warm things up a bit before your workout.
假如您没有其他需求  我得继续检查
If there's nothing else, I need to make sure
确保保龄球的重量没有标错
these balls are marked with their correct weights.
给他10号的鞋
Size 10 for him
给我一双有钢头的
and anything with a steel toe for me.
某人总是出纰漏[掉球]
Someone drops his ball a lot.
计划有变
There has been a change of plan.
你们的保龄球教练说在顶楼碰面
Your bowling instructor would now like you to meet him
要在按摩浴缸里热身
in the hot tubs for a warmup first.
-楼上见吧  -好
- Meet you up there? - ?Yep.
假如你想打给慈善机构换搭档
If you're calling the charity for a new partner,
那是行不通的
it's not gonna work.
他们已经做好海报了
They already made the posters.
-可以点餐了吗  -迫不及待
- Ready to order? - ?Very.
我来这间餐厅只想点一样菜品
I came to this restaurant for one thing and one thing only.
是什么菜
And that thing is...?
抱歉  来一份你们世上最肥...
Sorry. Uh, one of your world fa--
世上最肥的热狗  这就来
One of our world's fattest hot dogs coming up.
不  是肥美小汉堡
No! The-the slider.
肉饼要几分熟
And how would you like it?
我
Me...
-是的  您  先生  -要三分熟
- Yes, you, sir. ?- ...dium rare.
能请你送到泳池来吗
And can you have it delivered to the pool, please?
当然
Of course.
那份小汉堡送到泳池
Okay, that slider goes to the pool,
还有一份贝克汉姆先生的送到顶楼
and it looks like we need one for Mr. Beckham to the roof.
你见到过穿黑帽衫的家伙吗
You seen a guy in a black hoodie?
-他刚走  -谢了
- Just left. - ?Thanks.
我去去就回
Oh, I'll be back.
我迫不及待想尝尝你们世上最肥的热狗
I'm dying to try one of your world's fattest hot dogs.
你到商场了吗
Hey, you here at the mall?
还没  你怎么喘得这么厉害
No, not yet. Why are you breathing so hard?
一群孩子在我旁边抽电子烟
Oh, um, a bunch of kids were vaping next to me,
我不得不伏地爬到香薰店里
and I had to army-crawl into a-a candle store.
我来都来了  你想买什么吗
Yeah. Is there anything you want while I'm here?
我能告诉你我"真正真正想要的"吗
Can I tell you what I want, what I really, really want?
辣妹合唱团歌词
你正在看着我对吗
You're watching me right now, aren't you?
小卡  好吧
Cam, okay, look.
我只是希望能在健身房
I was hoping I'd run into Posh
遇到时髦辣妹聊上两句  好吗
here at the gym for a private moment, okay?
我们都希望遇到贝克汉姆夫妇
Look, we're both after the Beckhams.
我们一起制定一个计划
Let's come up with a plan together --
在泳池酒吧等我
meet me at the swim-up bar.
他们还有泳池酒吧
There's a swim-up bar?!
就是说  我们才该住在这里
I know, we should be living here
艾丽克斯该住在我们的破房子里
and Alex should be living in our stupid house.
希金斯  我需要你
Higgins, I need you!
你在哪
Where are you?!
您似乎遇到小麻烦了
A spot of bother, I see?
我做不到
I can't do it!
您当然可以
Oh, of course you can.
我爬到您身前
I'll just crawl in front of you
您就可以抓住我的腰
so you can grab me around the waist.
要是我笑出声了提前向您道歉
I apologize in advance for any giggling.
我这人天生很怕痒
I'm cursed with the tickle gene.
出什么事了
What's going on?
有人卡在滑梯上了
Someone's stuck on the slide.
她想爬回去  但是
She tried to climb back down, but --
-滑梯不许反悔[倒退]  我懂  -是啊
- No backsies, I get it. - Yeah.
那是我的
Oh, oh, oh! That's for me.
谢谢
Thank you.
-可是速度太快了  -不  别担心
- But it goes too fast! - Oh, no, don't worry.
我将不断收缩臀部来控制我们的速度
I shall vary the flex of my buttocks to control our speed.
我们会
We should be --
不
No!
请接受我最诚挚的歉意
My deepest apologies!
不
Oh, no!
好吧
Okay.
不
Noooo!!
麻烦解决
That one's sorted.
送一些气泡水到按摩浴缸帐篷
I need some sparkling water sent up to the hot tub cabanas.
不能说是给谁的
Can't say for whom,
但附带一杯香槟
but let's include a glass of champagne
以防他的"时髦"妻子一会儿也来
in case his posh wife joins him.
小心
Easy.
有没有搞错
Come on!
希金斯
Higgins!
听我说
Um, listen...
我需要你帮我弄来那个小汉堡[滑水者]
I need your help getting my hands on the slider.
滑水者吗
The slider?
当然
Oh, of course.
看着就诱人
Quite a looker, that one.
问题就在这  目前为止
Well, that's the problem -- so far,
我只能看  还没尝到
I've only been able to look and not taste.
无需多言  我会想办法将滑水者送来
Say no more. I shall find a way to deliver the slider to you.
太好了  有没有什么隐蔽些的地方
Great! Um, is there somewhere private
能让我单独享用它
where I could enjoy the slider alone?
我建议您去我们顶楼的按摩浴缸
Might I suggest one of our rooftop hot tubs
能眺望都市
overlooking the city?
完美  我在那等着
Perfect, I'll wait there.
我还需要一个围嘴  我总搞得满身污渍
And I'll-I'll need a bib -- I can make a mess.
还很脆
Still crisp.
他没走远
He's close.
我怎么又到这来了
How'd I get back here?
时髦辣妹
Ah, Posh.
多谢
Thank you.
您丈夫叫您去露台碰面
Your husband has asked that you meet him
一起在按摩浴缸里喝香槟
up in one of the rooftop hot tubs for some champagne.
菲尔
Phil.
希金斯  真正的敌人不是滑梯
Higgins! The slides aren't the enemy.
而是恐惧
Fear is.
见到我们的住客成长总是如此激动人心
It's always a thrill to see one of my residents grow.
顺带一提  某位神秘的先生
By the way, a certain mystery man
在楼内注意到了您的存在
has spotted you around the building
他希望您能去顶楼一聚
and has requested your presence on the roof.
杰总算知道搞浪漫了
Jay's finally doing something romantic!
我还以为他只是个不解风情的糟老头
Just when I thought he was a clueless grouch.
这地方有几个大堂啊
How many lobbies does this place have?!
打扰一下  哪里能买到泳衣
Excuse me. Where can I find a bathing suit?
所有帐篷里都有附赠的泳衣
Oh, there are complimentary suits in all of the cabanas.
别担心  我每晚亲自高温消毒
?Worry not, I boil them myself nightly.
机器人有这本事吗
Let's see a robot do that.
希金斯  我们有个不寻常的小请求
Hi, Higgins. We have a bit of an unusual request.
我们知道你必须谨言慎行  不过
Now, we know you need to be discreet, but...
我们希望能和某位杰出的英国人
we are hoping to have a rendezvous
来一场"不期而遇"
with a certain distinguished Brit.
我会为二位安排
Consider it arranged.
-好的  -好的
- Okay. - ?Okay.
还是没看到女士们的踪迹
Still no sign of the ladies.
或许她们是在另一个帐篷里
Maybe they're in a different cabana.
我的到了
Mine's here.
陪我等金发妹吧
Let's wait for the blonde.
我只有在成双成对的时候才玩得开
I only know how to do this with even numbers.
机器人先生
Hello, Mr. Robot!
能告诉我我的浪漫惊喜在哪里吗
Can you tell me where to go for my romantic surprise?
歌洛莉亚
Gloria?!
现在我的到了  但你的走了
Now mine's here, but yours is gone.
现在两个都跑了
Now they're both gone!
她们会回来的
They'll be back.
或许其中一个保姆出了问题
Maybe one of them had a nanny emergency.
去里面等她们吧
Let's wait for them in there.
小汉堡[滑水者]
Slider?
很快就到  请进3号帐篷等
Arriving shortly. Cabana 3.
谢谢
Thank you.
那事不宜迟  我们开始吧
Here we are, then.
希金斯  你在干什么
Higgins, what are you doing?!
要玩角色扮演啊
Oh, role play.
我知道我只是个低贱的马夫
I know I am but a lowly stable boy,
不允许进入主人们的住宿区域
unwanted in the master's quarters, but --
但或许你们会想要好好"教训"我呢
Perhaps you'd like to teach me a lesson?
别伤到脸就行
Just stay away from the face.
我们之间很明显有一些误会
Uh, obviously there's been some sort of misunderstanding.
我们看起来像是那种
Yeah, do we look like the kind of people
会喜欢跟别人玩奇怪角色扮演
that would be into some sort of weird role play
而且是带马夫情节的人吗
involving a stable boy?
我想他非常不乖
I'm assuming he's been naughty
会愿意做任何事来保住自己的工作吧
and would do anything to keep his job.
小卡  小卡
Cam -- Cam?
为自己辩护一下  我其实很常接到这种要求
In my defense, I do get this request quite often.
尤其是在圣诞节前后
Particularly around the holidays.
耶稣在马厩中出生
其实呢...
Actually, um...
我们很希望能跟某一对明星夫妇见面
we were hoping to meet a certain celebrity couple.
无需多言
Yeah. ?Say no more.
我不能做任何保证  但请两位稍等
I make no promises, but let me just
等我穿好裤子  出浴缸尽力安排一下
wriggle back into my shorts and make some inquiries.
来得真巧
Ah, wonderful timing!
请移驾3号帐篷  您的神秘男士正在等候
Please step into Cabana 3 -- your mystery man awaits.
你好啊
Hi.
我知道我们不应该偷偷在这里见面
I know that you and I aren't supposed to be here,
但经过我今天的经历
but after today,
我不想再被恐惧控制生活
I am tired of living a life of fear.
歌洛莉亚是克莱尔为我准备的棕发惊喜吗
Was Gloria Claire's brunette surprise?
起因是克莱尔送了我"乐园"的入场券
It all started when Claire gave me a free pass to Fun Town.
我就想  那今天来试试看
I thought, just try it today.
放胆去"玩"  看看感觉如何
Take a ride, see how it feels.
我以前都没发现你的脚那么性感啊
Oh. I never noticed how sexy your feet are.
谢谢夸奖  但我们真的不可以  歌洛莉亚
Thank you, but this isn't happening, Gloria! ?
你们在这里啊  抱歉我们晚到保龄球场了
Oh, there you are. Sorry we missed you at the bowling alley.
她绑头带时跟现在看起来不太一样啊
She looked different with a headband on.
先在按摩浴缸里暖身
Warming up in a hot tub first --
不是寻常套路  但只要能让小贝放松就行
unconventional, but, hey, anything to loosen up Becks.
我们有认识叫贝姬的吗
Did we meet a Becky?
或许吧  当时那么多女人
Maybe. There were so many of them.
所以小贝是几岁了来着
So, how old is this Becks?
44岁
44.
好戏上场啦
It's on.
你们在这里啊
Oh, there you are.
等等  你是小贝吗
Wait... you're Becks?
是啊  我也十分有心想学
Yep, and I'm eager to learn.
警告一下  我身材比较走形了  但我的腿功还是一流
A warning -- my form is clumsy, but I'm great on my feet.
好吧  男的谁来
Okay, who gets the dude?
这件事从未发生过
This never happened.
行吧  我来处理他
Fine, I'll take him.
但我跟他就只是先熟悉一下再看情况啊
But we're just gonna hang out and see where it goes.
抱歉打扰了
Pardon the interruption.
看来您已享用完滑水者[小汉堡]啦
It looks like you're finished with the slider?
是啊  我能说句实话吗  我喜欢面包[屁股]大点
I am, and can I be honest? I prefer bigger buns.
偶尔能这样男人与男人间聊天  感觉很不错吧
It's wonderful to just talk like men sometimes, isn't it?
是啊
It is.
杰  你怎么来了
Jay, what are you doing here?
我花了一天的时间在找一个王八...
I've spent the whole day looking for that miserable --
你就是那个毛衫美食家吗
You're the Foodie in a Who-dy?!
你为何会这么认为呢
W-Why would you say that?
番茄酱
Ketchup!
我很努力了  但真的没听懂你的话
I'm trying, but I'm lost!
你侮辱了我妈
You insulted my mother!
天啊  你是厨巨王走吗
Oh, my God. You're Close to Utlaw?!
是橱柜狂徒
It's Closet Outlaw!
杰  你生气我不怪你
Jay, I don't blame you for being mad.
我让我的粉丝大军去喷了你  还有...
I-I turned my legions of fans against you, and, uh...
其实是叫帽衫美食家啦
it's Foodie in a Hoodie, by -- by the way.
但我刚听说你家有个比这个严重多了的问题啊
But you got a bigger problem at home that I just heard about,
我觉得我能帮到你
and I think I can help you with it.
-克莱尔  -歌洛莉亚
- Claire? - ?Oh! Gloria.
真不敢相信你能认出我
I can't believe you recognized me.
我的头发真是很对不起了
I'm so sorry about my hair.
我很高兴我们终于可以聊这件事了
I'm so glad that we can finally talk about it.
你就放心让它长吧  让你自己当个女孩
Grow it out, let yourself be a girl.
好的  最后的安排
Okay, final set of instructions
今天的一切绝对会是我将要出版的回忆录
on a day that will no doubt be a memorable chapter
《有何能效劳》中  十分精彩的篇章
in my forthcoming memoir, "You Rang?"
您  去2号帐篷
You, Cabana 2.
您  去3号帐篷
You, Cabana 3.
你真浪漫
You are romantic.
亲爱的  如果你不喜欢我的头发  我可以改掉
Honey, if you don't like my hair, I can change it.
什么  我很喜欢啊
What? I love it.
或许下周我可以给你安排
Maybe next week I can arrange
与红发女郎的一场约会
a little rendezvous with a redhead.
好的
O-Okay.
消除刚才的误会真是太好了
I'm glad we cleared that up.
我真是等不及要跟你上保龄球课了
I can't wait for my bowling lesson with you.
天啊
Oh, my God.
帽衫美食家今天来过这里呢
Foot-y in a Hoodie was here today.
你真是太棒了
Ah, you're great.
时髦辣妹什么时候来呢
When does Posh get here?
很抱歉迟到了
And I apologize for being late.
我其实有给你语音信箱留言呢
You know, I-I left a message.
抱歉错过了你的电话
I'm sorry I missed your call.
你能再说一次这句子吗
Can you say that one more time?
我收到了昨天的杂项费用账单
So, I got a few incidental charges from yesterday.
200块钱的甜心宝宝购入费
Two hundred dollars for sugar babie procurement.
抱歉
Sorry.
还有8个小汉堡以及1瓶椰子水
Eight sliders and one coconut water?
那瓶水他也收我钱啊
He charged me for that?
300块钱的滑水道救援费
Three hundred dollars for a slide rescue.
40块钱的使用健身单车后未清洁的罚款
Forty dollars fine for the non-wiping of stationary bike.
我都没怎么流汗啊
I barely sweat.
你现在就满头汗了吧
You are sweating right now.
150元的护腿未还罚款
A hundred and fifty dollars fine for the non-return of legwarmers.
8张100块钱的西部世界门票
And eight one hundred dollar west world entry fees?
天啊  我们把小卡忘在那里了
Oh my God! We left Cam there.
糟了
Oh no!